knox.edu 2017-02-01

# Privacy Policy - Knox College

This policy applies to web pages residing under the subdomains www.knox.edu, hello.knox.edu, and apply.knox.edu.

## Our Commitment to Privacy

Knox College is committed to protecting your privacy and recognizes the importance of privacy to individuals and businesses visiting this website. Any information you voluntarily provide to us through this website will never be sold or traded to other colleges, universities, nonprofit organizations or businesses. Questions regarding this policy should be directed to: [web@knox.edu](mailto:web@knox.edu).

## Information Gathered Automatically When You Visit This Website

Each time you visit this website or open an e-mail from the College, the College may automatically collect the following information:

  * The Internet Protocol address of the computer used to access this website.
  * The date, time, and duration of visits to each page of the website.
  * The web page from which you accessed the visited page.
  * The browser type, version, and the operating system it is running on.
  * E-mail clicks and other actions taken.

This automatically-collected information is used to improve the content and structure of this website and to help the College understand how users are interacting with the website and e-mails sent by the College. This information is aggregated and used for statistical analysis by the College itself and through the use of third-party analysis tools. The College does not sell or trade this information for use by any other entity.

The College also uses cookies (unless you block them) and tracking pixels to aggregate analytical information about the user experience of the website and to provide custom marketing activities for users of the website. These can be set by the College or third-party services authorized by the College. While no personally-identifiable information is automatically gathered through these methods, the College may link tracking information with personally-identifiable information that is voluntarily provided by the user.

## Information Voluntarily-Provided

At points while visiting this website, we may ask you to provide personally-identifiable information such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, or phone number. The College will never sell or trade personally-identifiable information unless we have your consent. The College could also be required to provide this information in response to a subpoena, court order, or other legal requirement.

When you e-mail the College, your e-mail address and contents of the message, including text and any attachments, are saved. This information will be used to respond to you, address issues you have identified with the website, improve the user experience of the website, or forwarded to the appropriate campus office for response. Your e-mail address is not sold or traded to any other entity.

At any time while visiting this website, you may decline to provide any requested information.

## External Links

Pages on this website may include links to external website not owned by or affiliated with Knox College and, therefore, not subject to this Privacy Policy. You will need to check the privacy policies of these individual sites to see how their operators handle your personal information. Knox College is not responsible for the policies or content of such websites.

## Advertisements on External Websites

Knox College may use services to advertise on third-party websites. This could mean the College advertises to past visitors of this website who may not have supplied any voluntary information. These services use cookies to track past visits of this website and other websites visited. Any information collected by the College from these services also follows the practices of this Privacy Policy and the policies of the services used.

## Information Protection

Though no data collected over the internet is completely secure, we have taken reasonable steps to protect the data collected through this website.

## Your Consent

By using this website, you consent to the collection and use of the information described in this Privacy Policy by Knox College. We may periodically update and make changes to this policy and reserve the right to do so; any changes will appear on this page.
